{
        "quizTitle": "HTML Heroes",
        "quizSynopsis": "How familiar are you with HTML? Select the correct answer to these ten common technical interview questions and see where you stand.",
        "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
            "Hypertext Markup Language",
            "Hypertext Mockup Language ",
            "Hypertext Model Language",
            "Hypertext Middle Language "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which line of HTML code will open a link in a new tab?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "<a href=\"#\" target=\"#blank\"></a>",
                "<a href=\"#\" target=\"-blank\"></a>",
                "<a href=\"#\" target=\"_blank\"></a>",
                "<a href=\"#\" target=\"blank\"></a>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "3"
            },
            {
            "question": "How many different types of HTML headers exist?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "10",
                "6",
                "4",
                "1"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "2"
            },
            {
            "question": "How do you leave a comment in HTML? ",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "// COMMMENT",
                "*/ COMMENT",
                "<--COMMENT-->",
                "<!--COMMENT-->"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4"
            },
            {
            "question": "What are the three types of HTML lists?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "Ordered, Unordered and Definition",
                "Ordered, Unordered, and Dictionary",
                "Ordered, Unordered, and Table",
                "Ordered, Unordered, and Combined "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "1"
            },
            {
            "question": "What are the three types of HTML lists?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "Local and Session ",
                "Local and Distance",
                "Cookie and Session ",
                "Internet and Session "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "1"
            },
            {
            "question": "Which of the following HTML tags produces a horizontal line?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "<hl>",
                "<hr>",
                "<br>",
                "<line>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "2"
            },
            {
            "question": "Which HTML tag does not come in a pair?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "<div>",
                "<a>",
                "<span>",
                "<img>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4"
            },
            {
            "question": "Which of the following is a block level element? ",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "<span>",
                "<a>",
                "<img>",
                "<div>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4"
            },
            {
            "question": "Which of the following is an inline element>?",
            "questionType": "text",
            "answers": [
                "<span>",
                "<div>",
                "<p>",
                "<h1>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "1"
            }
        ]
    } 